{
    "subject": "resource/Boxing_Legends_of_the_Ring",
    "predicate": "property/modes",
    "object": "resource/Single-player_video_game",
    "human_readable": "Boxing Legends of the Ring is played in single-player video game mode.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9787228107452393,
            "question": "Is there a single-player mode available in Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8396481275558472,
            "question": "What is the main gameplay mode in Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7925490140914917,
            "question": "What type of game is Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7731842398643494,
            "question": "Is Boxing Legends of the Ring a competitive game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6367406249046326,
            "question": "Can you customize your boxer in Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5791821479797363,
            "question": "Can you play Boxing Legends of the Ring with other people?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5596502423286438,
            "question": "How many players can participate in Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5335248708724976,
            "question": "Does Boxing Legends of the Ring offer multiplayer options?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.532325267791748,
            "question": "What type of sport is simulated in Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5251036286354065,
            "question": "Can you compete against AI opponents in Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Boxing Legends of the Ring is played in single-player video game mode.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6648_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of sport is simulated in Boxing Legends of the Ring?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6648_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Boxing Legends of the Ring offer multiplayer options?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6648_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many players can participate in Boxing Legends of the Ring?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6648_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6648_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6648_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6648_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6648_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6648_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6648_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6648_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6648_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6648_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6648_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents describe various gameplay modes for \"Boxing Legends of the Ring,\" including career and battle modes, implying a single-player experience. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents describe various gameplay modes for \"Boxing Legends of the Ring,\" including a career mode where players can create their own boxer and fight through all other boxers leading up to a title match. This supports that the game is played in single-player video game modes."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}